Tabi Machi Late Show
First Night
"Recipe"
You don't want to forget about it,
so always set the timer.
Pomodoro sauce should have
a nice, full flavor,
so I make it using butter.
Once it's spread out evenly, add the stock.
You put in a lot, I see.
Yes, put in a lot.
Boil down the tomato sauce first.
That way...
Its savory flavor is further condensed.
Thanks for waiting.
Here's dinner.
Let's eat.
What's the matter?
How...
does it taste?
There's nothing
wrong with it.
Yeah,
it's good.
You had to make pomodoro
for the first time once
yourself, right, Azuma-san?
Oh? That's a funny thing to ask
out of the blue, Nagi-kun.
Did you...
look up a recipe or anything?
Well... I was taught.
Very patiently taught.
Starting with how to boil the spaghetti.
To start by setting the timer?
That's just like me!
So do you add any of your
own personal touches to it?
I do, but it's nearly the same
pomodoro as yours is now.
The
flavor of your pomodoro has always
been my aspiration.
So you've said.
Many times.
Ever since you first made it at my house...
Since I was able to start this job...
And in the three years
since you took me in...
In the beginning, your pomodoro
was the flavor I strived for.
But the more I tried,
the more I realized I could
never reach your level.
"How did Azuma-san get her pomodoro
to taste the way it does?"
When I thought about that,
I finally realized that it wasn't
you I should be watching,
but what you, yourself, were looking at.
After my two years in Milan,
starting two days from now,
I'll come back as a chef
with the ability to look much farther
into the distance, like you.
So until then, Azuma-san, please...
Please keep watching over me.
Thank you so much for
these past three years.
Thank you, as well.
Silly...
There's no secret to my pomodoro's flavor.
I guess this is how it feels
to be given too much credit.
I was like you once.
I only now understand
how selfish it is to make
someone your role model,
and how cowardly I was to not
try to stand at your level.
Once it's spread out evenly, add the stock.
You put in a lot, I see.
Yes, put in a lot.
The strange guilt you feel when
someone looks up to you...
The awkwardness,
the responsibility,
and the separation.
So now I'm sending off a second.
Did you say something?
Just talking about the former
owner of that suitcase.
What? It's not yours?
Don't worry about it.
Go on, now. Go!
Azuma-san!
When I come back to Japan,
let's have a contest to find
out which tastes better,
my pomodoro or yours!
I'll squash you!
I'm heading out.
Oh?
He left?
Yep.
I just hope he doesn't come back before
he's finished, like someone else I know.
Right?
You know, I wish you wouldn't
just give away my old suitcase.