Tabi Machi Late Show
Second Night
"Transistor Smartphone"
Reloading
Koizumi-san.
This is a story of the
memories I have with her.
Oh, yeah...
I guess you don't know my name, huh?
I'm Kumeno.
I look forward to spending this
year with you, Koizumi-san.
Koizumi-san was my classmate.
She didn't make friends with anyone,
and she was always hiding somewhere
on school grounds to ditch class.
Koizumi-san doesn't talk much.
You want to put me in your
collection of friends that much?
We finally have some time to just talk.
So, Koizumi-san...
Why are you always by yourself?
Why are you always messing with your phone?
Want my email address and mobile number?
You picking a fight?
You don't mind being alone?
You don't actually get lonely sometimes?
Not as much as you, probably.
But you always seem so impatient,
and it makes me feel bad for you.
So I thought I'd reach out to you, you know?
Huh?
Give it a rest.
You think if you just
flash that creepy smile,
anyone will become your
friend, just like that?
Well, don't!
You know you want friends.
Not one like you.
I think I understand you quite well, though.
You stop walking when you see me,
and you make eye contact with me a lot.
Oh, just be honest with yourself.
Come on!
Maybe...
Maybe you think being that way
lets be who you want to be...
But frankly, you might
want to drop that act.
Huh?
You don't have it in you, even if...
Koizumi-san.
...you've got the popular
honor student act...
Koizumi-san.
...down to an art right now.
You deserve more pity than I do.
Don't underestimate me.
Fine.
Until you fly off the
handle one of these days,
I'll be your friend.
Look at me!
D—
Don't start crying...
Ugly.
Wa—
Wait!
I think I understand you pretty well, too.
Isn't that why you started talking
to me in the first place?
That was the last time
Koizumi-san and I spoke.
Even after we graduated,
what she said to me that day was
like a thorn I couldn't pull out.
Once I finished college and got a job,
the little fortress of smiles I'd built
crumbled and fell within a year.
And now, I've managed to
truly make it on my own.
That's the story.
Good times.
What should I have said to her
when she stopped me that day?
Would I have had a chance to
break things off with her?
Still, you should've been more
honest with yourself, too.
Kumeno Akie
This account does not exist.
Maybe you only ever realize who
you should have been friends with
after it's already too late.
Message sent
Damn it...
I'm sorry for what I said back then.