Tabi Machi Late Show
Third Night
"Summer Festival"
All done.
Don't get too rowdy, okay?
Hey, what's the Lantern Festival about?
Well, it's when people who have
passed away come back to this world.
People who have passed away?
So I'll get to see Haruka-kun again?
Yes...
You just might get to see him.
Otaiya Festival
And... Pull! Pull! Pull! Pull!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
The Lantern Festival is when
people who have passed away
come back to this world.
Y-Yukari-chan...
Wow! The Lantern Festival is amazing!
I really did get to see you!
Y-Yeah...
We promised we'd go to the summer
festival together this year!
Yeah.
I'm so happy!
Come on, let's go!
Come on!
Hey, wait...
Did you finish the summer homework?
Uh, no, not yet...
I know, right?
I don't have anything done, either!
Come on, hurry!
That was so much fun!
That was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah...
Yeah.
What's wrong?
You won't disappear?
If I... If I move my hand
and let go of you...
Will you disappear, Haruka-kun?
Will you? Will you disappear?
I won't disappear.
Even if you move your hand...
Even if we say goodbye for today...
If you call for me,
I think...
I can
be with you anytime.
Okay!
The Lantern Festival is when
people who have passed away
come back to this world.
Come get some!
Now you've done it!
Let me play, too!
Hey, it's Haruka!
What are you doing?
Where've you been all night?
Oh, uh... I...
What's wrong?
You look kind of pale.
No...
Nothing's wrong.
Where should we go next?
I wanna go to that one stall!
I've gotta get home...
My mom told me not to stay out late.
C'mon, play a little longer.